Guide to the Harry L. Carr Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Harry L. Carr papers
1962-1972
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
2210
2210-001
Carr, Harry L.
0.42 cubic feet (1 box)
Papers of a trade union official of Seattle, Washington
Trade union official of Seattle, Washington. In addition to his labor activites, Carr was the former president and business Representative of Carpenters District Council; president, King County Labor Council; board member, Forward Thrust; member, Seattle City Planning Commission; member, Civic Center Advisory Committee; board member, Greater Seattle Inc.; vice-chair, Metro Action Committee, 1957; vice-president United Good Neighbor Fund, 1958; director, Seattle Convention and Tourist Bureau, 1959; Board member, Seattle World Trade Center, Inc.; co-chair Citizens Emergency Committee for traffic and recreation, circa 1960.
Correspondence, speeches, minutes, and reports, chiefly concerning Carr's activities as president of Carpenters' District Council, Seattle, Washington. Includes material relating to AFL-CIO, King County Labor Council of Washington, American National Red Cross, Seattle Maritime Advisory Board, and Washington State World Fair Commission.
No restrictions on access.
Donated by Mr. Harry L. Carr, 12/20/1973.
Carr, Harry L.$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Century 21 Exposition$d(1962 :$cSeattle, Wash.); American Red Cross; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America.$bDistrict Council (Seattle, Wash.); Central Labor Council of Seattle and Vicinity; Forward Thrust (Seattle, Wash.); American National Red Cross.$bSeattle Chapter.$bService to Military Families Committee; Citizens' Port Committee (Seattle, Wash.); Maritime Advisory Board (Seattle, Wash.); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Labor History; Labor Unions; Civic Activism; Washington (State); Seattle; Oral Histories
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - General Correspondence, 1948-1972 (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - Speeches and Writings (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - AFL-CIO conference, 1959-1963 (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - Ephemera - Carpenters (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - Ephemera - AFL-CIO (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - Labor News, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- Carpenters and Joiners of America, District Council, Seattle - Right to Work (Box 1)
- Central Labor Council, King County - Incoming Letters, 1957-1964 (Box 1)
- Central Labor Council, King County - Seattle, Century 21 Exposition - Incoming Letters, 1959-1962 (Box 1)
- Central Labor Council, King County - Seattle, Century 21 Exposition - Clippings, 1962 (Box 1)
- Central Labor Council, King County - Seattle, Century 21 Exposition - Ephemera, 1962 (Box 1)
- Forward Thrust - Organization (Box 1)
- Forward Thrust - Incoming Letters, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
- Forward Thrust - Reports/Minutes, 1966-1972 (Box 1)
- Forward Thrust - Speech by James Ellis, 1962 (Box 1)
- Forward Thrust - Clippings, 1968 (Box 1)
- Red Cross, American National Red Cross, Seattle Service to Military Families Committee - Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 1)
- Red Cross, American National Red Cross, Seattle Service to Military Families Committee - Miscellaneous (Box 1)
- Seattle, Citizen's Port Committee, 1960 (Box 1)
- Seattle Mayor, Maritime Advisory Board, 1971-1973 (Box 1)
- Personal Papers (Box 1)